dspconcepts.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy | DSP Concepts

### GENERAL DECLARATION

We at DSP Concepts are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to your data that we collect within your visit of [www.dspconcepts.com](http://www.dspconcepts.com/) website.

We periodically update this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

You are free to use our website without providing your personal information. When you visit our website or submit a registration form, we ask you to provide some personal information.

We collect, store and use your personal information to ensure proper permission to access our tools and for contacting you:

\- We ask you to provide your name so we can address you the right way.

\- We ask you to provide your company name, so that we can properly check for licensing permission.

\- We ask you to provide your email address for several reasons:

  * to respond to your requests
  * to negotiate project details
  * to send you our latest corporate updates
  * to suggest you better offers
  * we may contact you to ask for your feedback on our services

\- We use third-party services (see sec. ‘Third Party Services’ of this Policy) that are tracking your location and IP-address. We collect this data to contact you at a time that is most suitable for your region and for understanding and analysing the main flow of audience to our website.

### NO DATA DISSEMINATION

We collect and store your personal data only for the internal use and to ensure you have the best experience while working with us. We do not give your personal information to third parties. In case we do have a need to give your personal information to a third party, we will make sure that it happens in a legitimate and secure way. We will do our best to restrict the information which is passed on to the barest minimum. We will never sell your personal information.

### THIRD PARTY SERVICES

#### Google Analytics

This website uses the "Google Analytics" service to analyse website visits user’s behaviors. We do this to improve user experience on our website. Google Analytics is operated by Google Inc. (USA). Google Analytics uses "cookies" - text files that are stored on your device. The information collected by the cookies is usually sent to a Google server in the USA and stored there. IP anonymisation is used on this website.

Click on the following link to disable Google Analytics: Disable Google Analytics. For more information on how Google Inc. uses your data, please visit: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

### COOKIES

This website uses cookies to process information about standard log information and details of your behavioral patterns upon visiting our site. We do this to facilitate the use of certain functions and to enhance your user experience.

Cookies are small data files that are stored on your device for record-keeping purposes. We store this information in a pseudonymized user profile. We do not process cookie-based information to identify individual users.

You have full control over the use of cookies. You may deactivate or restrict the transmission of cookies by changing the settings of your browser.

### “SENSITIVE INFORMATION”

According to GDPR, processing of personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, and the processing of genetic data, biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying a natural person, data concerning health or data concerning a natural person’s sex life or sexual orientation shall be prohibited.

Our website does not collect and does not ask you to provide any ‘sensitive data’.

### ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OVER PERSONAL INFORMATION

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. If you provide us with your personal information, you may ask us to do the following:

  * have us provide you data we have about you, if any

  * have us change/correct any data we have about you

  * to request that your user information not be used to contact you

  * have us delete any data we have about you

  * express any concern you have about our use of your data

You may unsubscribe from our marketing emails and newsletter at any time. After unsubscription, we will delete your email address from our list of subscribers.

You can exercise any of these rights by contacting us at [info@dspconcepts.com](mailto:info@dspconcepts.com). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe and notify you of the action we have taken.

### CONTACTS

In case you have any questions regarding your personal data, please, contact us via email address [info@dspconcepts.com](mailto:info@dspconcepts.com)
